# **RESUME**

Name: Poon Chun Yeung

Address: TBC (Arrive Manchester on 22-Jun)

**Phone (Mobile): +852** 97134012

Sex: M

Whatsapp: +852 97134012

Telegram: <a href="https://t.me/Neverstopdown">https://t.me/Neverstopdown</a> Website: <a href="https://bit.ly/3DbJ3eo">https://bit.ly/3DbJ3eo</a>

Linkdln: https://www.linkedin.com/in/chun-yeung-poon-5278b1163/

### **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

Dec 2016-Dec 2016 Red Hat Asia-Pacific

RH124 Red Hat System Administration I

Jul 2015-Sep 2015 Systematic

IBM Certified System Administrator

Sep 1998-Jun 2003 **Buddhist Hung Sean Chau Memorial College** 

F.1 to F.5

#### WORKING EXPERIENCE

## **ONESULTION Ltd**

May 2018- May 2022

Position: Infrastructure Engineer

#### Job duty:

- Networking (Firewall setup, security, network design, management)
- Wireless Solution (In & Out-door AP setup
- Window Server upgrade project
- O365, SharePoint administration
- Active Directory admin work
- Device installation task (Server, AP, Rack, Network devices, PC)
- SSL-VPN with remote office project
- Relocation project
- Backup & Replication solution
- End Users support
- Documentation (Training Guide, Inventory, Project plan)
- P2V project (VMWare, Hyper-V)
- Monitoring System setup (PRTG)
- Email administration (Zimbra, Exchange, Rackspace)

### **Courtesy Services Co Ltd**

Oct 2017- Dec 2017

Position: IT Helper

#### Job duty:

- In-House IT support (NAS, Desktop, ERP, Network, Printer)
- Project Coordinator
- Media editing (AI, Video)

### **Kelly Service Hong Kong**

Oct 2016- Aug 2017

Position: Senior Technician

#### Job duty:

- Active Directory (Account admin, Group, Policy)
- Lotus Notes (Account and Group setup, Restore)
- Netbackup (DB restore)
- Linux/Unix (Account control)
- Sybase (Account control, DB restore)
- Networking (Cisco switch port, Troubleshooting; Firewall security rule control \*Brand: CheckPoint, Juniper)
- WSUS (Windows update patch control)
- Cisco IP Phone (Manage on CUCM, Configuration, Troubleshooting)
- VMWare (VM create, migration, management)
- Hand over procedure, project
- Softeware installation (SQL, Sybase, MS Office, Lotus Notes, etc)
- Reaporting

## **Global Technology Integrator Ltd**

May 2015- Sep 2016

Position: Technical / Project Leader

#### Job duty:

- PC, Printing, Server hardware maintenance (HP. EPSON)
- Server installation (Rack mount, OS base)
- Software installation & upgrade project (Project leader)

#### **TECHNOLOGY SKILLS**

- Virtualization (VMWare, Hyper-V)
- Networking (TCP/IP, Firewall, Switch)
- Backup Solution (Veeam)
- Server upgrade, setup. migration (Host, OS)
- Security (Server, Network)
- Server administration (Active Directory, O365, Exchange, FS)
- Wireless Solution (In & Out-door)
- Project management
- Windows, MacOS support
- SSL, BOVPN
- Site Infra design

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

- Cantonese (100%)
- English (40% Speaking, 60% Wirting)
- Mandarin (75%)

#### \_\_\_\_\_\_

#### **ABOUT ME**

Hello, I'm CY,Poon, Infrastructure Engineer from Hong Kong. I will arrive UK on Jun-2022.

Base-on Hong Kong working style, I had many different projects, brand devices experience, also include administration and project management work.

Network security and server project is the most-high percentage on my job duty, otherwise, administration (Server / Network), desk-side support and paper also my schedule workload.

My lovely hobby is basketball, and learning some new technology, seems like video editing, coding, phonographic.

And my English not speaking very well.

Hope we can be teammate on future, have a nice day!

**EXPECTED SALARY: N/A** 

**AVAILIABILTY:** After 04-Jun-2022